Finding Aid for the Grand Ole Opry Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Photographs
  - York Brothers [Found in Folio of Songs], 1943 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 56)
  - Six unknown men in white jackets [bluegrass band?], Faron Young, T. Tommy Cutrer (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 57)
  - Troops watching performance (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 58)
  - Troops watching performance on hill outside (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 59)
  - [Marines?] watching performance (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 60)
  - Troops watching performance. Woman in audience. (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 61)
  - Hank Snow signing autograph for soldier (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 62)
  - Hillous Buttram-bass, Hank Snow-guitar, unknown man-guitar (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 63)
  - Texas Troubadors: Billy Byrd-guitar, Dickie Harris-pedal steel (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 64)
  - Jack Drake-bass, Ernest Tubb (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 65)
  - Ernest Tubb and the Texas Troubadors performing for troop. (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 66)
  - Ernest Tubb-guitar, Billy Byrd-guitar,Dickie Harris-pedal steel (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 67)
  - Unknown man-fiddle, Jack Drake-bass, Hank Snow, Denise Webber-flight attendant, Billy Byrd-guitarist, unknown man (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 68)
  - [Koreans?] at barbed wire fence. (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 69)
  - Encampment with troops (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 70)
  - Unknown man- lap steel. [Member of Hank Snow’s band] (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 71)
  - Banner,“Grand Ole Opry,” on Elmer E. Fryer building (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 72)
  - Banner, “Grand Ole OPry,” on Elmer E. Fryer building (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 73)
  - Banner,“Hank Snow - Grand Ole Opry - Ernie Tubb” (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 74)
  - Hank Snow-guitar, unknown comedian (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 75)
  - Hank Snow and Korean youngster (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 76)
  - Ernest Tubb singing autograph for soldier (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 77)
  - Unknown comedian, Hank Snow-guitar, Hillous Butram-guitar, unknown steel lui tar player (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 78)
  - Unknown group performing for troops (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 79)
  - 2 unknown men standing before [Quad Lightning?] sign (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 80)
  - Unknown man checking parcels in front of plane (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 81)
  - 2 unknown men standing before [Quad Lightning?] sign (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 82)
  - 2 unknown men in uniform (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 83)
  - Troops watching Hank Snow and band outside (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 84)
  - Unknown man in suit near bridge (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 85)
  - Unknown comedian and unknown man [members of Hank Snow’s band] (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 86)
- Poster Fragments (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - “Patsy Cline of Decca Records - Manager and Booker Randy Hughes” (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Picture of Patsy Cline (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - “Welcome D.J. ’s and Sincere Thanks” (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - “Opry Stars and Band” (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Admission tickets, “WSM Grand Ole Opry’s 40th Birthday Celebration,”, October 21-22-23, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Roy Acuff and His Smoky Mountain Boys at the Grand Ole Opry” Leaf from picture book (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “WSM’s 10th Annual Country Music Festival,” November 3 and 4, [1961] Flyer with pictures of performers (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Music City U.S.A.” layout of map for “WSM’s 7th Annual National DJ Festival Celebrating the Grand Ole Opry’s 33rd Birthday”, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “The Grand Ole Opry ... ”reproduction of advertisement from March 24,[1957] issue of Tennessean. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Hear the Grand Ole Opry” Grand Ole Opry advertisement for WOAY radio, Oak Hil, West Virginia. Newspaper clipping. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Every week new G-E live-color cameras ... ” General Electric advertisement for Grand Ole Opry television show. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Nashville Scrapbook, by R. Goffo, ‘Uncle Dave Macon, The Dixie Dewdrop’” layout., November 15, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Original Old Guard (National Life). List of people in a 1922 photograph of the Original Old Guard during a convention in Nashville. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Flyer with pictures of Cowboy Copas, Hawkshaw Hawkins, Patsy Cline, Randy Hughes, and Jack Anglin (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Movie posters (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - “Hi, Neighbor” 2 placards (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - “0, My Darling Clementine” 1 placard (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - “Second Fiddle to a String Guitar” advertising campaign (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - “Smoky Mountain Melody” poster, stored in map case in Vanderbilt Special Collections (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Recorded Discs - 45 r.p.m. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Pet Milk’s Grand Ole Opry SO-325/26 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - [Side 1] “Pet Milk’s Grand Ole Opry Connnercials” (3) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - [Side 2] “Pet Milk’s Grand Ole Opry Talent Contest, Special Message to Pet Milk Salesman [sic] by T. Tonnny” (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Starday 708 Cowboy Copas (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - [Side 1] “Black Eyed Susie” by L. Copas/T. Hill (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - [Side. 2] “Won’t You Ride in My Little Red Wagon” by Rex Griffin (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Recorded Disc 33 1/3 r.p.m. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Republic RLP 904 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - “Del Wood Encores; Del Wood at the fiano” (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Interview Tapes (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Interview Tapes are stored in the audio-visual area of Vanderbilt Special Collections
  - George D. Hay, “10 Stories” - 3 tapes (Box 6, Folder 11, Folder 1)
  - Loretta Lynn and Loyd[sic] Evans, KGBX Springfield, Missouri, 5:40 a.m. - 1 tape (Box 6, Folder 11, Folder 2)
  - Tex Ritter and Audie Murphy with Hairb Hensley “at the end of tape” 3 May 1967 - 1 tape (Box 6, Folder 11, Folder 3)